PAVEL ZAPLETAL



Personal

Name: Pavel Zapletal

Birth date: 10.7.1994 Nationality: Czech

Driving license: B

Social media

Facebook: Pavel Zapletal Instagram: Pavel_kapaak LinkedIn: Pavel Zapletal

Contact

Phone: +420 776 324 294

Email: pavel.zaplet25@gmail.com Address: Brno, Pod Nemocnici 11

Web: pavelzapletal.cz

Skills

JavaScript / TypeScript

React / Next

Express / Nest

CSS / SCSS

HTML / JSX

Adobe

Java

Languages

English German

About me

I am a web development enthusiast with experince in building and designing websites. I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience in React and Next.js. When it comes to graphical design I enjoy working with Adobe Xd.

Education

Electrotechnical high school 2009 - 2013

Mohelnice

Focus on Informatics

University of Ostrava 2020 - today

Ostrava

Applied Informatics

Experience

Dixons Carphone CoE s.r.o. 2021 - today

Junior JavaScript Developer

Learning and working with the newest web development technologies, e.g. React, Next.js and Nest.js.

HELLA AUTOTECHNIK NOVA s.r.o. 2016 - 2020

Specialist Patent Search

Protecting company's patents and searching for competitors in patent database Orbit. Communication with English / German speaking collegues.

HELLA AUTOTECHNIK NOVA s.r.o. 2016 - 2016

Operator

Assembly of automobile headlights.

Kimberly-Clark s.r.o. 2014 - 2014

Operator

Machine operator.